那个小费给大富翁假钱的混球
Whoever tipped me in monopoly money
可以死去监狱了
can go directly to jail.
一块钱假钞吗
A dollar?
都用假钱了 他们小费还照样给这么少
Fake money and they're still under-tipping.
你看 我就喜欢看到
Oh, look. I love it when people
别人给宠物天竺鼠穿上可爱制服
dress guinea pigs up in adorable costumes.
阿憨 你看起来像贝比·鲁斯
Han, you look like Babe Ruth.
不 是婴儿·鲁斯
Well, Baby Ruth.
滚你们俩丫了个蛋[亲我屁股]
Maybe you two can kiss my sweet ass,
我这制服跟全垒打一样棒好吗
because this outfit's a home run.
我要组一个队去参加餐厅界棒球联赛
I'm putting a team together for the restaurant league.
阿憨 我很乐意加入 但你也知道
Well, Han, I would play, but you know,
我有屁股问题
I've got this hip thing,
我有"太潮不打球症"了
meaning, I'm too hip.
你们俩个呢
What about you two?
相信我 我可是个棒球高手[玩蛋蛋高手]
I'm telling you, I'm a great ball player.
不 我才是玩蛋蛋高手
No, I'm a great ball player.
我懂如何同时握住
I know how to cup
还给我的蛋蛋搔痒
and tickle mine at the same time.
我是说美国人最爱的娱乐消遣啦
I'm talking about America's favorite pastime.
我这招也是啊
Oh, so am I.
我加入 我有威猛的投球手臂
Well, I'm in. I have a really good arm.
去那边吧 阿憨 我们来丢个几球
Go over there, Han. Let's have a little catch.
好的 准备来吧
All right, here we go. All right.
再退一点 再退[深]一点 阿憨
Go deep. Go deeper, Han.
这话绝对"不会"有女人对他说
A phrase no other woman will ever say to him.
投球吧 使出全力 不用怕
Throw it, and don't be afraid to bring the heat.
力道过猛了
Too much heat.
一球 双杀蛋 本局结束
Ball one...and two. Game over.
我好像忘了穿这制服最重要的那部分了
I seem to have forgotten a crucial part of my uniform.
需要杯子[护裆]吗 阿憨
Need a cup, Han?
两位女士 请在这里等
You ladies can wait in here.
布莱恩 在我爸进来前
Brian, before my father comes in,
他的精神状况如何
how are his spirits?
以一个要面对六十到一百年
You know, for someone who's looking
刑期的人来说
at 60 to 100 years in prison?
还算不错
Pretty good.
我现在去带他过来
I'll bring him right in.
小布 今天有人被杀咩
Hey, Bri, anyone get killed today?
麦克斯 你每次都问这问题
You ask me that every time, Max,
我也每次都回答你
and every time I tell you,
这是关押高智商罪犯的监狱
it's a white collar prison.
懂了 那有人被高档钢笔捅了吗
Got it. Anyone get shanked with a Mont Blanc pen?
布布 还有件事
Yo, B, one more thing.
监狱剧集《破茧威龙》里 犯人每次
On Lock Up: Raw, they always spray the guards
都会泼粪跟尿 所以...
with a mixture of urine and feces, so--
麦克斯 你能别每次都提这事吗
Max, please, can we go one day without you mentioning that?
我挺好奇我爸为啥要我们
I wonder why my dad wanted us
今天立刻赶来见他
to rush out here and see him today.
他想要来一发"情人探视"吧
He probably wants a conjugal visit.
-麦克斯 -别这么大反应
- Max! - Relax!
是跟我来一发啦
With me.
你们来啦 我生命的光芒
There they are, the light of my life
-以及她的保镖 -老爸
- And her bouncer. - Hi, daddy.
麦克斯
Hey. Max.
直接就上啦 不来点前戏吗
Oh, we startin' this? No foreplay?
抱歉让你们俩大老远跑来一趟
Listen, I'm sorry to make you come all the way out here
而且还是坐"地铁" 我都不忍心说这词
on the--God help me--subway,
但我其实需要你们帮个忙
but I actually need a favor.
帮我逃狱
Help me break out.
开个玩笑啦
I'm kidding.
老爸 你有心情开玩笑是很好
Daddy, it's so amazing you can joke,
但不要在麦克斯面前开 好吗
but maybe not around Max.
她已经放话要替你活剥狱卒的皮
She's already offered to skin a guard alive
让你披着人皮走出去
and walk you out of here wearing him.
你明明知道这招可行
Well, we know it works.
听我说
All right, listen.
这个以前在我手下工作的女人
This woman who used to work for me
要被人以百万美元收买
is being paid a million dollars
写一本我的私密全揭秘档案
to write a tell-all book about me.
一百万啊
A million dollars?
那我写一本卡洛琳的揭秘书能拿多少钱
How much can I get for a tell-all book about Caroline?
第一章 "边睡边放屁"
Chapter one: "Sleep farts."
麦克斯 你能别每次都提这事吗
Max, please, can we go one day without you mentioning that?
那女人的名字叫珊卓拉·罗森索
The woman's name is Sandra Rosenthal.
卡洛琳 你记得她吗
Caroline, do you remember her?
记得 那个履历上说谎的女人
Yes, the one who lied on her resume.
那个加法都算不好 而且更离谱的是
The one who couldn't even add, and worse than that,
她还穿衣还黑色配棕色
she wore brown with black together.
我就喜欢黑色配棕色啊
I like brown and black together.
我知道
I know.
等等 为什么有人愿意出这么高价啊
Wait, why would anybody pay that woman so much?
她说她有你什么把柄
What is she saying she has on you?
她声称自己被解雇
Well, she's claiming she was fired
是因为她知道整起庞氏骗局的
because she had insider information
内幕消息
about the ponzi scandal,
还说自己跟我发生过关系
and that we were sleeping together,
-但其实没有 -当然没有
- which we weren't. - Of course you weren't.
你才不可能睡一个
You would never sleep with someone
穿黑配棕色的女人呢
who wore brown with black together.
50年代后 我就没看过有人
Man, I haven't seen this much hatred
对黑跟棕色[人种]这么严重的鄙视了
toward brown and black since the '50s.
总之 我想先知会你这件事
Anyway, I wanted you to hear it from me first,
因为她准备上皮尔斯·摩根的访谈节目
because she's about to go on Piers Morgan live,
然后她就会大放厥词 胡说八道
and she can say whatever she wants.
不会的 因为我会去驳倒她的谎言
No, she can't, because I'll be there to refute her lies.
我会以尊严与格调
I'll defend you with dignity and class
外加地铁上捡的新唇膏 来替你辩护
and my new lipstick I just found on the subway.
皮尔斯·摩根呢 那家伙可牛逼了
Wow, Piers Morgan. That dude's legit.
不但主持节目 还有一家家具店
He's got a show, he's got Piers 1 Imports.
小公主 没有你我真不知道怎么办
I don't know what I'd do without you, princess.
你是我唯一能信赖的人
You're the only person I can trust.
好了 你先走吧
Now, get out of here,
我有些话想单独跟麦克斯说
'cause I gotta speak to Max privately for a second.
好吧...
Oh...Sure.
-好吧 我... -快闪边吧
- Okay, I-- - Just go.
你爹爹想跟我"单独聊聊"呢
Daddy wants to talk to me privately.
-宝贝 我爱你 -老爸 我也爱你
- Love you, sweetie. - Love you, daddy.
布莱恩 我就在门口等
Brian, I'll just be right outside.
麦克斯...
So, Max...
你知道我只是耍耍嘴皮子的吧
You know I'm all talk, right?
我想你帮我跟卡洛琳说件事
I need you to tell Caroline something
这事我不好意思对她说
I couldn't bring myself to say.
那女人也宣称
This woman is also claiming
我有只"小小鸟"
I have a small penis.
等等
Wait.
所以你留我来"赏鸟"洗刷污名吗
So I stayed behind to see it?
不是啦
No.
我想让你告诉卡洛琳 让她做好心理准备
I want you to tell Caroline so she'll be prepared,
我蛮肯定她就是靠这个谎言
'cause I'm pretty sure that's the lie
来让那本书大卖
that got the book sold.
她这谎水分多"大"
How big of a lie?
相信我 非常"大"
Oh, a really big one.
你都跟我爸聊了些什么
So, what did you and my father talk about?
我不想告诉你 我难以启齿
I don't want to tell you. I'm uncomfortable.
你也会难以启齿吗
You're uncomfortable?
这事肯定很严重
This must be bad.
我就没见你有过难以启齿的话
You've never been uncomfortable in your life.
他染毒了 得癌症
Is it drugs? Cancer?
还是他在监狱里有了基友
Oh! Did he fall in love in prison?
我能接受这事 你可以告诉我
I'll be fine with it. You can tell me.
我家还有钱的时候 我常去参与林荫大道
When we had money, I was very active in the Park Avenue
直人支持基门卫联盟的活动
straights for gay doormen alliance.
他们这是怪胎帮派
Is this some kind of weird gang,
还是刚有比赛结束啊
or did a game just let out?
麦克斯 你就告诉我嘛
Max, come on. Tell me.
好吧 那女人会说你爸爸有个"小...
Fine, the woman's gonna say your father has a small--
先生 你的呜呜祖拉又吵又过时
Sir, your vuvuzela is very loud, and very 2010.
我爸爸有个什么
My father has a what?
他有个"小...
He has a small--
拜托了 比赛都结束了
Seriously, the game's over.
像你这种人居然还还结婚了 真是理解不能
And how on earth you have a wedding ring is beyond me.
那女人要说我爸什么
What is she gonna say about him?
-我听不到你 -她会说...
- I can't hear you! - She's going to say...
你爸爸有只"小小鸟"
your father has a small penis!
他觉得我来告诉你会比较不尴尬
He thought it'd be less awkward if I told you.
有咩
Was it?
我真服了那叫珊卓拉·罗森索的女人
I can't believe that Sandra Rosenthal woman.
这又是一个弥天大谎
There's another lie.
-怎么说 你见过吗 -当然没有
- Why, have you seen it? - No, I haven't seen it!
我这辈子都不想看到
I never want to see it.
你看过你爸的鸡鸡吗
Have you seen your father's penis?
有的话 它也是在跟我挥鸡告别
If I did, it was waving good-bye.
麦克斯 我想了很多
Max, I've thought a lot about it,
我不能就这么让那女人
and I can't sit there while that woman
就这么在主持人面前谈我爸的鸡鸡[甩他脸上]
waves my father's penis in Piers Morgan's face.
你该庆幸这主持人不是安德森·库珀
You're lucky it's not Anderson Cooper,
因为他肯定会笑得花枝乱颤
'cause he'd be giggling up a storm.
我有个计划
I have a plan.
我上节目就是要证明那女人的话是假的
My goal on this show is gonna be to discredit that woman
而且要告诉大众 虽然我爸爸做过坏事
and tell people, even though my father did a bad thing,
但其实他也做过很多好事
he did some wonderful things as well.
这是他联合国儿童基金会帮忙
Look, here he is working with UNICEF.
这是他帮忙海地灾民重建家园
Here he is rebuilding haiti.
这张只是一张他玩划水的帅照
Oh, this is just a cute picture of him water-skiing
是在太浩湖的慈善活动上呢
at a charity event on Lake Tahoe.
给没钱买高尔夫球杆的白人募款吗
What's the charity? White men without golf clubs?
反正我是那么计划的啦
So that's my plan, and hopefully,
希望上完节目后
going on that show will put an end
能让坊间关于我爸的谣言停止
to all these ridiculous rumors about my father.
卡洛琳
Hey, Caroline.
怎么啦
Yeah.
外面都在传你爸有只"小小鸟"
The word on the street is your dad's got a weenis.
苏菲 你上哪听来的
Sophie, how did you hear about that?
奥列格告诉我的
Oleg told me.
消息出现在我的谷歌鸡鸡搜索警报
It came up on my Google penis alerts.
我喜欢在时事尖端 跟随流行"鸡"态
I like to keep current, see what the trends are.
你也不会想当一个长着别人
You don't want to be that middle-aged guy
多年前就有的同款鸡鸡的中年男子吧
wearing the same penis you had in high school.
这下好了 网上传遍了
Great, now, it's all over the internet
我肩膀都耸起来到我耳旁了
And my shoulders are all up around my ears.
你看 紧张到都没办法对那女骗子
Look, I'm too tense to even shake my head "no"
摇头反对了 这可是我最重要的动作呢
at that liar woman, which was gonna be my key move.
我好需要按摩 但我又没钱去
I need a massage, but I'm broke.
卡洛琳 我可以帮你按摩啊
Caroline, I'll give you a massage.
准备好迎接失望的结尾
Get ready for a sad ending.
还有失望的开头以及过程
And beginning, and middle.
来啦
There.
爽吧
Oh, yeah.
感觉如何啊
How does that feel?
感觉像小蜘蛛在我肩膀上跳舞
Like baby spiders are dancing on my shoulders.
你是我见过第一个
You're the first Asian I've seen
不会按摩的亚洲人
that can't give a massage.
卡洛琳 我请你跟麦克斯
Hey, Caroline, I'll treat you and Max
去我那家高档美容院按摩吧
to a massage at my fancy spa.
好啊 我从没去过呢
Cool! I've never been to a spa.
我做过最接近按摩的事
The closest I've been is sticking my arm
也就是把手臂伸进药局里的血压测量计
in the free blood pressure machine at Walgreens.
等等 那是给手臂用的吗
Wait, that's for your arm?
谢谢你帮我按摩 阿憨
Thanks for the massage, Han.
你人真好 你还在按啊
It was very nice-- Oh, you're still doing it.
我完全没感觉
I had no idea.
这真是爽歪了
That was a-mazing!
一男的揉了我身上整整一小时
I mean, a guy rubbed me for an hour
而且完全不用我肉偿
and didn't expect anything back?
按摩这玩意必须得火啊
This massage stuff could catch on.
我按摩时还是无法宣泄自己的压力
I could not let go during my massage.
这里可以"宣泄"的吗
Oh, was letting go an option?
我当时都差点要"泄"了 但我怕才按到一半
I was close, but I didn't want to get halfway there
就会因为我"宣泄过度"而被人赶出去
and have the management throw me out or something.
我真的好紧张
I'm just so tense.
皮尔斯·摩根常会问很难的问题
Piers Morgan asks some difficult questions.
上周他才问了一部无脑卖肉电影的演员们
Last week, he asked the Spring Breakers cast
对最近北韩的形势有何看法呢
their thoughts on the North Korea situation.
抱歉
Sorry.
麦克斯 这里是静修室 我们得安静点
Max, this is a quiet room. We have to be quiet.
女孩们
Hi, girls!
我要来喝杯高档纯净水了
Oh, I'm getting myself some fancy water.
他们有柠檬 橙子 跟黄瓜呢
Look, they got lemon, orange, and cucumber.
感觉跟老虎机里一样
It's like a slot machine over here.
我刚才享受了人生中最棒的竹子按摩
Oh, I just had the best bamboo massage.
他们不停的用竹子打我
Oh, they kept whacking me with it
直到我承认我七岁那年偷了条面包才停手
until I confessed to stealing that bread when I was seven.
真是如释重负啊
Oh, what a load off.
卡洛琳 你看起来还是有点紧绷
Caroline, you still look a little tense,
不过想到你要上国家电视台
but I guess having to talk about your father's junk
谈论你爸爸的"小鸟" 的确压力很大
on national television will do that to a girl.
我不会在节目上
I will not be speaking about
谈论我爸爸的"鸟"
my father's "junk" on television.
不行 我明天不能出来吃午餐
No, I can't have lunch tomorrow.
我要上皮尔斯·摩根的节目
I'm doing Piers Morgan live.
你不会相信刚才发生了什么事
You won't believe what just happened.
你加入了邪教吗
You joined a demonic cult?
珊卓拉 那个写揭秘书的女骗子
Sandra, the liar writing the tell-all book,
刚刚走进来了
just walked in.
她也来一日美容之旅啊
She's getting a day of beauty too?
这大概是最基版的大战前训练地了
This is like the gayest training for a fight ever.
珊卓拉
Sandra?
这边
Right this way.
脸朝下躺
Lay face down.
你先放松几分钟 我马上过来
I'll give you a few minutes and I'll be right back in.
很好 我超需要做按摩
Perfect. I really need this massage.
宣传我的新书真是累死人了
Promoting my new book is exhausting.
如果像是在自夸 那真是抱歉啦
I'm sorry if that sounded braggy,
但当一切如鱼得水时
but I guess that's how you sound
人说起话来也趾高气扬
when things are going so great for you.
那位可怜的按摩师要被迫听她
That poor masseuse is gonna be forced to listen to
喋喋不休地抱怨她那本烂书
her yammer on about her dumb book.
不过话说回来 我刚一直对我那位按摩师说
But then again, mine had to hear me constantly say,
"不要害怕这对大胸器"
"don't be afraid of the boobs."
我们应该去听听她怎么说那本烂书
We should be hearing about that dumb book
好让我知道该出什么招
so I know what I'm up against.
前提是 得想办法进那个房间
If there was only a way to get in that room.
人生没有过不去的坎 也没有进不去的地方
Oh, anyone can get into any room if they really want to.
你真的觉得2004年的游艇展面试
I mean, do you think that I was invited
我是受邀进去的吗
to the audition for the 2004 boat show?
真的 快去吧
Yeah. Go.
我来对付那个按摩师
I'll take care of that masseuse.
苏菲 你不会伤害她吧
Sophie, you're not gonna hurt her, right?
不会 我会先用小费打发她
No. I'm gonna try tipping her first.
我回来了
I'm back.
没错 刚才在走廊里的人是我
Yes, I was just out in the hall with you,
现在在房间里的人也是我
now, here I am in the room with you,
都是同一个人
the same person.
头别抬起来 不要往上看
Just keep your head down, don't look up,
放轻松
and relax.
你不会一直说个不停吧
You're not gonna talk a lot, are you?
不会 但你可以随意说
No, but you should feel free to.
无论是你的想法 还是你那本书
whatever's on your mind or in in that book.
什么
What?
-那是什么声音 -那个吗
- What was that? - That?
那是我 一个人
That's just me, alone,
用能量和声音营造出一种治疗氛围
creating a healing space with energy and sound.
音量越大越有效
Lots of sound.
听说你在写一本大作
So you're writing a big book.
想跟我分享下内容吗
Do you want to tell me all about that?
这本书是关于马丁·钱宁
Well, it's about this guy, Martin Channing.
他人非常好 非常值得尊敬
Oh, he is very nice and very respectable.
你看了我的书之后 就不会这么想了
You won't think that after you read my book.
我要狠狠地捅他一刀
I am really gonna stick it to him.
好了 你现在简直是在使劲推我
Okay, now, you're just pushing me.
你是怎么...
Uh, how did you--
你是怎么做到的
Uh...How-- how did you do that?
感觉好像你有三只手
It feels like you have three hands.
这说明我很厉害
That's how good I am.
这应该是热石按摩疗法
This is supposed to be a hot stone massage.
马上给您做
Comin' right up.
热石
The hot stones.
好啦 热石来了
All right, here come the ho-o-ot stones.
对 就这样 真舒服
Oh, yeah. Yeah, that's nice.
我开始觉得放松了
I'm really loosening up.
那让你再放松多一点
Oh, well, then let's loosen you up some more.
再来点石头
More stones.
More stones!
我那本揭秘书能拿到一大笔钱
Yeah, I'm got paid a lot of money for my tell-all book,
所以我真的会全盘揭秘
and I am really gonna tell all.
放错了 别放那里
Not there! Not there.
这是怎么回事
What? What is going on in here?
珊卓拉 事情是这样的
Well, what is happening here, Sandra,
你要去国家电视台上大放厥词
is you're about to go on national TV
当着全美国人的面胡说八道
and tell America lies about my father.
他从未跟你发生过关系
He never slept with you.
那他也从未在你卧室的粉红公主床上
Did he never sleep with me in your bedroom,
跟我发生过关系吗
on your pink canopy bed?
你心知肚明 根本没发生过这种事
You know what? That never happened.
那真是荒唐 你是个疯子
That's insane. You're crazy.
反正没人能证明谁对谁错
Well, it's my word against yours.
你一定会在电视上丢人现眼
You're gonna be very embarrassed on TV.
但你最丢脸的时刻 是在美容院大厅
But not as embarrassed as you're going to be in the spa lobby,
因为我要告诉大家 卡洛琳·钱宁对我实施了
when I tell everyone that I was touched inappropriately
不当的身体接触
by Caroline Channing.
你不会告诉任何人的
You are not gonna tell anybody that.
谁管得住我
Who's gonna stop me?
姑娘们
Hey, girls.
我刚一直在门外面听着
I was listening outside the door.
有啥问题吗
Everything okay?
麦克斯 我不知道我是否能应付
Max, I don't know if I can do this.
万一珊卓拉说的是事实呢
What if Sandra's telling the truth?
她的确知道我有张粉红色的公主床
She did know about my pink canopy bed.
她怎么会知道的
How would she know that?
因为全世界都知道芭比有一辆粉红小车
Because everyone knows barbie comes with a dream car,
一匹粉红小马 还有一张粉红公主床
a pony, and a pink canopy bed included.
他来了 皮尔斯·摩根真人
There he is. There's Piers Morgan, live.
你觉得现在就管他要家具店折扣
Do you think it's too soon to ask him
是不是有点太唐突了
to give me a discount at Piers 1?
他看着挺高尚的 估计不会问鸡鸡的事情
He looks dignified, like he's not gonna ask about a penis.
但如果他问起来怎么办
But what if he does?
-麦克斯 我好害怕 -把手机给我
- Max, I can't do this. - Give me your phone.
你得时刻提醒自己
You need to remind yourself
你父亲以前的样子
of the person your father used to be.
瞧 这是他跟联合国儿童基金会共事
Look, here he is working with UNICEF.
这是他在"富人湖"里滑水
And here he is water-skiing on "Lake rich person."
瞧那个笑容 是不是...等下
Look at that smile. Is that the smile of--hold up.
他泳裤左裤腿冒出来的是什么东西
What's coming out of the left leg of his swim shorts?
我觉得你爸的鸡鸡在试图告诉我
I think your father's junk is trying to tell me
离冬天还有六个星期
there's gonna be six more weeks of winter.
你在说什么啊
What are you saying?
我是说 有人的"鸟"不小心探头出来了
I'm saying, someone had a tip slip,
而且那只"鸟头"还不小哦
and that is not a small tip.
作为一名服务员和一名荡妇
And as a waitress and a loose woman,
只要我看见头 我就知道那只鸟大不大
I know a small tip when I see one.
看这里
Here.
抱歉 抱歉
Sorry, sorry.
她刚给我看了安妮·海瑟薇的新发型
She just showed me a picture of Anne Hathaway's new haircut.
这不错
Well, this is good,
因为能证明那女人在撒谎
because it can proves that woman is lying.
对啊 你可以把这拿给皮尔斯看
Yep, you just have to show this to Piers.
我说过 我绝不会提及[靠近]我爸的鸡鸡
I told you, I'm not going near my father's penis.
我只需指出
All I have to do is point out
那女人根本不懂理财和金融
that that woman has no finance skills.
不像她 我们要采取高尚的手段
Unlike her, we are taking the high road.
麦克斯 你是把照片发你手机上吗
Max, are you sending that to yourself?
今天的嘉宾是珊卓拉·罗森索
I'm here with Sandra Rosenthal,
她刚签了一份超值钱的书约
Who's just signed a huge book deal
揭发臭名昭著的金融家
to do a kiss-and-tell
马丁·钱宁的种种隐私
on disgraced financier Martin Channing.
-欢迎你 珊卓拉 -你好 皮尔斯
- Welcome to you, Sandra. - Hello, piers.
谢谢你邀请我上台讲述我的故事
Thank you for allowing me to tell my story.
只是个故事而已
It's a story, all right.
我们十分想听
Wow, so we're right into it.
好的 让我先介绍下
Okay, well, let me catch up.
另一位嘉宾是卡洛琳·钱宁
My other guest is Caroline Channing,
马丁·钱宁的女儿 说得委婉些
daughter of martin Channing, who, to put it mildly,
她声称罗森索女士的书
is claiming that your book, Ms. Rosenthal,
完全就是狗屁连篇
is a bunch of bull.
没错 皮尔斯
That's right, Piers.
按你们英国人的说法
It's pure rubbish,
就是"通篇胡扯"
as your people say.
那完全是你们美国人的说法
That was perfectly American.
好吧 那先从你开始
Right, then, let me start with you.
事情是这样的 推动罗森索女士作品的
Well, to catch everybody up, Ms. Rosenthal's large book advance
最"大"动力 是她揭露某物的真相是...
really has to do with something that turned out to be,
用你的话来说 "非常小"
by your words, very small.
有何评论 钱宁小姐
Comments, Ms. Channing?
我不发表任何评论 皮尔斯
I'd rather not comment about that, Piers,
因为我有格调 但我的确有个问题
because I have class, but I do have a question
要问我父亲曾经聘用过的珊卓拉女士
for Ms. Rosenthal, who was hired by my father
因为她声称自己是金融学的学士
because she claimed she had a degree in finance.
珊卓拉女士 一辆载有27个人的火车
Ms. Rosenthal, if a train carrying 27 passengers
早上9点离开中央车站
leaves Grand Central Station at 9:00 A.M.,
于下午5点到达800英里外的芝加哥
travels 800 miles to Chicago, arriving at 5:00 p.M.,
请问火车的速度是多少
how fast was it traveling?
这个嘛
Well, I--
超简单的数学题 皮尔斯
Simple math, piers.
每小时100英里
100 miles an hour.
-你说什么 -你问题的答案
- I'm sorry? - That's your answer.
抱歉 我也算是个数学高手
Sorry, I'm a bit of a mathlete.
真厉害
Impressive.
我也有个数学问题要问你
I've got a math equation for you.
如果一辆3英寸长的"火车"开进"隧道"
If a 3-inch train is entering a tunnel,
那"隧道"能感觉到吗
do I even know it's there?
女士们 这不是毛里·波维奇无下限的节目
Ladies, this isn't Maury Povich.
皮尔斯 我只是单纯想说明
Piers, I am simply trying to illustrate
如果她够格胜任金融工作的话
that she should have been able to answer it,
她应该可以回答那个问题才对
had she been qualified for her job in finance.
我书里所写的一切内容都是真的
Everything that I am writing in the book is true, Piers.
我说的任何东西
There is nothing that I have said
她都无法证明是假的
that she can prove is untrue.
等下 为什么会有个女人在我桌子底下
Wait a minute, why is there a woman under my desk?
有吗 皮尔斯
Oh, is there, Piers?
没错 我的父亲是骗了很多人的钱
Yes, my father defrauded a lot of people,
他也为此付出了代价
and he's paying a price for that,
但她为了自己的利益而消费我父亲时
but I'm not gonna sit by silently while she exploits him
我绝对不会袖手旁观
With lies for her own gain.
皮尔斯 我想告诉您
Piers, there's so much about my father
很多关于我父亲的事情 比如...
I want you to know, like he--
这是什么
What is this?
我知道这是什么
Well...I know what this is.
我也有一根
I've got one.
但这是谁的 为什么要给我看
But whose is it, and why am I looking at it?
那是我父亲的
It's my father's.
他的"鸟"不小心探头了
He had a bit of a tip slip.
女士 我不知道你想要什么样的男人
Madam, I don't know what you're looking for in a man,
但这个男人
but this...
明显是"神雕大侠"
is far from inadequate.
老实说 与你描述差距太远
In fact, it's so far from inadequate,
我要马上结束本期访谈
that I'm bringing this interview to an immediate close.
你和你的书都没有任何可信度
Your book and you lack any credibility.
到此为止
That's it.
"你能帮我搞到皮尔斯家具店的折扣吗"
"Can you hook me up with a discount at Piers 1 Imports?"
很可能某天出版商会对你有兴趣
Hey, you know, they'll probably come to you one day
想出一本你的揭秘书
and want a tell-all book.
记住第一章已经有了 "边睡觉边放屁"
Remember, we already have chapter one, "Sleep farts."
第二章是 "我的新后妈 麦克斯"
Chapter two: "My new stepmom Max."
麦克斯 我会一辈子都得替我爸辩护吗
Max, am I gonna have to defend my father forever?
可能吧 但别担心
Probably, but don't worry,
-我会帮你的 -谢谢
- I'll be there to help. - Thank you.
因为保卫丈夫 是妻子的职责
'cause it's a wife's job to defend her husband.
我一想到他要在监狱度过余生
It makes me sad to think he's gonna be in prison
就觉得很难过
for the rest of his life.
别这样想嘛 他不是在监狱
Don't think of it like that. He's not just in prison.
他是在非洲跟联合国儿童基金会共事
He's in Africa working with UNICEF,
他在海地
He's in Haiti,
他在"富人湖"上滑水
he's water-skiing on "Lake rich person,"
他还在我电脑的桌面上
and he's on the desktop of my computer.
我应该删掉那照片
I should delete that.
我的手机放哪里了
Where'd I leave my phone?
天啊 你们不会是在看我爸的照片吧
Oh, god, are you guys looking at the picture of my dad?
是的 钦佩不已啊
We are. Respect.
敬仰之情有如滔滔江水 连绵不绝
So very much respect.
我见过更棒的
Eh, I've seen better.
每天低头就能看见
Every day.
还给人家啦
Give me that.